In East Blue. there was a man
known as the "Great Gold Pirate".
His name was Woonan.
In countless harsh battles. Woonan
robbed many enemles of thelr gold.
Legend has it that the gold he stole
piled up as high as a mountain...
...and lit up the ocean at night as bright as day.
However. over the course of a few years...
Woonan's existence faded.
The Great Gold Pirate hid all his
treasure on a small island and then died.
That rumor is still alive even now...
...as many pirates are still trying to find this island.
There's a map drawn
by a member of Woonan's crew.
Whoever gets that map can locate the island.
A place where a mountain
of gold is said to lie in wait.
A legendary island!
The Great Gold Pirate.
I finally got it.
This is Woonan's treasure map...
Wealth. fame. power.
Gold Roger. the King of the Pirates.
attained everything this world has to offer.
And so. many men
head for the Grand Line
to find the great treasure
he left behind. the One Piece.
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
Wearing the straw hat sworn upon
him by the great pirate. Shanks...
Monkey D. Luffy heads out
to the sea on a journey
on the road to become King of the Pirates!
arittake no yume o kakiatsume
We're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashimono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
rashinban nante jûtai no moto
Compasses only cause delays
netsu ni ukasare kaji o toru no sa
Delirious with fever. I take the helm
hokori ka butteta takara no chizu o
If the dusty treasure map has been verified. it's not a legend!
tashikameta no nara densetsu ja nai!
kojinteki na arashi wa dareka no
When it comes to personal storms.
biorhythm no katte
simply ride aboard someone else's biorhythm.
omoi sugoseba ii!
and pretend it isn't there!
arittake no yume o kakiatsume
We're going to gather up all our dreams
sagashimono o sagashi ni yuku no sa
and set out in search of something to find
pocket no coin sore to You wanna be my Friend?
A coin in my pocket. and do you wanna be my friend?
We are. we are on the cruise!
We are!
I'm starving.
The last time we ate was a week ago.
The clouds look tasty.
I can't even drool anymore...
The gold island where
Woonan buried his treasure...
if the information I gathered is correct...
...it should be nearby.
All that I need to find ls the treasure map.
Did you find anything to eat?
Don't scare me like that. Luffy!
What on Earth are you thinking?!
I got.got. got. got it. finally got it!
This pole is really heavy.
This has to be the
largest elephant tuna in the world!
Brace yourself. you're gonna
eat until your stomach explodes!
Just kidding.
I'll never fall for that joke.
It's here. I got it... it's coming!
If this goes on for two more
days we'll all starve to death.
Of all things. who's fault is it
that we are all starving?!
I worked very hard to store one month's
worth of food for this long journey...
And who exactly ate it all in three days?
Luffy. it was you. wasn't it?!
Two days!!
Don't brag about it!
Anyways. go catch a bird or a fish or something!
You're so useless!
Oh...! What's this?
It's empty.
A grain of rice!
What? A grain?!
It's stuck on the lid! It must be luck!
Stop! It's mine!
Pathetic... I was an idiot.
Why did I ever join these idiots?
Oh. hello.
That's my treasure...
Who are you people?
I'm sure you are perfectly
aware of who we are.
So long!
Everyone come! Thieves!
Thieves? Are they bad people?
Who knows. those treasures
were stolen in the first place.
That's true.
They're bad people!
Then I'll give you these
in exchange for the treasure.
Oh. they are good people!
Delicious.
They are not good!
All right. let's go. kid.
Ah. I got it.
Hey! I need some more rice balls...
Hey Nami. they are bad people!
That's what I told you in the first place!
Hey. you shot me!
I was really surprised!
I-I'm sure I hit him...
Shoot him. shoot him!
Gum-Gum...
Rocket!!
What the...?
What?!
Crap. I jumped too far.
Wh-What the hell is this guy?
It's like his body's made
of rubber or something.
Rubber?
That's because I'm a rubber man.
Rubber man?
Don't tell me... he's a Devil Fruit
user like El Drago-sama?
El Drago? Who's that?
What're you doing?
Hey Luffy. be careful!
That...
El Drago-sama!
That pose. don't tell me...
He's gonna use his devil power!
Run!
What the...?
My treasure!
Hey. don't you think the
guy on that ship looks strange?
I thought I was gonna to die!
What was that?
I feel heavier.
Who's this? ls he one of them?
You've got to be kidding!
You dare say that to the great pirate Tobio?
Great pirate Tobio?
That's right!
I'm on a journey to
find the treasure island...
...but I was caught by
El Drago and forced to work...
No. that's not it!
I pretended to join them
in order to find the gold island.
I'm starving...
Is there food around here?
Hey. you listening to me?
That wonderful aroma is...
Wh... what?
What the?
Oden!
Oden?
What's all the commotion?
Tobio?
Grandpa Ganzô.
How many times are you going to
run away before you are satisfied?
You always run away and
then come back a few days later.
Whatever!
I'm here because my underlings were hungry.
so I thought l'd feed them some oden.
Underlings?
Hey. don't eat without my permission!
Delicious!
I've never had such good oden.
Your grandpa's cooking
is the best in the world!
He's just a stubborn old man.
His Oden is good. but that's all.
Every single day he commits himself
to making oden. but for what?
There's not many customers either.
I'm tired of this poor life.
That was good.
Ehh. there's no more!!
Luffy. damn you!!
I will never be a man like Grandpa.
I want to be a great pirate like Woonan.
Woonan? That gold pirate?
Ah. that's mine!
You bastard. I'll kill you!
It is said that the legendary pirate Woonan
stole one third of the world's gold.
Also. he only stole gold from evil men.
If you are not evil.
then he won't steal from you.
He is a very proud pirate.
Then he should be pretty strong. right?
I thought that he died a long time ago.
He's alive!
Woonan is not dead!
I'm sure Woonan is somewhere
on the gold island right now!
I heard that El Drago
is going to the gold island...
I have a pretty good idea where that is.
I'm going to ask Woonan
if I can be one of his crew.
All right. I'm going to meet this Woonan guy too.
If he's a good guy. I'll ask him to join my crew.
What are you thinking about?
Why would Woonan join your crew?
Because I'm gonna be King of the Pirates.
King of the Pirates?
Yeah!
I'm going to the Grand Line to find
the great treasure. One Piece.
And then I'll be King of the Pirates.
And as the King of the Pirates. it's only natural
that I should have a legendary man in my crew.
Cut the crap!
Stop joking around and
just say what you want to say!
Why don't you just say that I'll never
be able to join Woonan's crew.
What're you talking about?
Hey. kid.
I know it's hard to believe...
...but he's serious.
You guys...
Whatever you do. don't forget
about one very important thing.
What very important thing?
Do you guys have any money on you?
125 kamodoki. 153 seaweed.
302 fish balls. 102 white radishes. konjac.
fish cakes. eggs. etc. etc...
I. Ganzô. prepared this oden with my soul.
Added up. it costs 11 berries.
I want you to pay it.
11 berries?!
Is that expensive?
It's cheap! It's less than getting a nosebleed!
But...
No money!
No money?!
Yep!
Don't brag about it!
I guess I can't help it...
Luffy?
Thanks for the meal.
This is a token of my gratitude. keep it.
"Future King of the Pirates (Luffy)"
That was good. Pops.
Thanks.
Hey. Zoro. what's wrong?
That's called...
That's called eat and run!
What was that?
Are you complaining
about my daily vocal training?
Of course not. El Drago-sama.
But. it almost hit us.
It's your own fault for being there.
I... I guess.
Right. right. we just got
our hands on some nice treasure.
Is it gold? If it's not. throw it out.
You've got to be kidding!
Those treasures are mine!
Hey. can you see it yet?
It should be around here.
You've got to be kidding!
Those treasures are mine!
Hey. can you see it yet?
It should be around here.
That map... don't tell me...
I see it!
The gold island!
Woonan's Gold Island!
We've finally found it!
The Gold Island...
Now I know the island's location...
All that's left is for me is to get the map.
The Going Merry!
That means...
That's...
Usopp!
What a great nap!
Oh crap. I'm late. I'm late!
I'm late for my date!
Ow!
Who are you?
You don't know the great Captain Usopp?!
You're not that great!
Maybe he is the same as us. looking
for the treasure on this island...
Lo... Looking for treasure?
What's going on here?
Who the heck are these guys?
Gorashi.
Do it!
You guys shouldn't be so hasty...
Stop!
If you kill me. you won't
be able to find the treasure...
Ever!
What?!
Do you know where the treasure is?
Of course I know.
If you take this famous
treasure hunter. the great Usopp...
I'll show you places where you can find
diamonds. rubies. sapphires etc. etc...
Diamonds and Rubies...
Sapphires and others...
Kill him!
Why?
What I want is...
Gold!
G-Gold. of course! I know where
a mountain of gold is buried!
Gold!
What's wrong with this guy?
Where is it?
Of course. I will show you.
But without a map.
l can't really show you where it is.
Here's the map.
No way.
You really have one...
This is a treasure map?
The great pirate Woonan's greatest treasures.
Woonan?
It's Woonan's treasures?
"The treasure sleeps..."
"Look to the hill from the south..."
"If the whale faces west. then the tail..."
The writing is smudged after that.
so we can't read it.
If the whale faces west...
The tail is to the east.
Of course. the tail obviously points to the east!
Which means the treasure is in the opposite
direction to where the whale faces.
I see. so that's how it was.
These guys are freakin' idiots.
All right. let's go people!
Wait. I'm going too?
Of course.
You're kidding!
You always make me worry...
It's them. after all!
I'll pretend I didn't see them.
Damn you old man.
you didn't have to go so far.
I told you that we'll pay
for it by working on the ship!
Having him work for me is enough.
Eat and run people should just shut up.
I didn't run!
Then can you pay the bill?!
I see. now I understand
why you brought us to this island.
You're going to make us look for the gold.
Shut up!
Oh Tobio!
Can you get that for me?
It's very important.
Hurry up and keep cleaning!
If you keep day-dreaming like that
you won't grow up to be like me!
What? Don't decide what to do for me!
When did I ever say I want to sell oden?!
Don't talk back to me. you powerless midget!
Just do what I say!
Cut the crap!
You always talk about the freakin' oden!
Is the oden that important?
I've had it!
I'm going to find Woonan...
and I'll never come back again!!
Ah. my hat!
Wait! Give it back!
Tobio!
Pops. I'll definitely pay you back for the oden!
Don't worry!
Tobio...
What is this?
It's a whale right?
If the whale faces west.
The tail points to the east.
That means the treasure is...
That's it!
Tobio!
My hat.
Ah. that's right.
Great!
Okay. let's go back. Zoro.
What. You're sleeping?
Man...
You guys...
I'd have to be strong to
join Woonan's crew. right?
I don't think I'm strong enough
to join the way I am now...
Then just become stronger.
I have my ambitions.
and you have your ambitions.
Which means you should just keep
walking forward towards that goal.
You...
What a simpleton.
See ya.
The coast. which way is it?
Hurry up and keep walking.
I got it already!
I'm pretty sure that the gold is somewhere
around that castle we just saw.
The problem is. where in that castle.
No problem. this guy knows. right?
Of course I know. I was close friends with Woonan.
What. with Woonan?
That's right!
If you dare doing anything to me. Woonan's
crew won't take it lying down!
Woonan's crew is no longer a part of this world.
What? What does that mean?
It means we took care of them already.
with our own hands.
What did you say?
The last guy we killed had the map.
The map shows the island
where Woonan's gold lies.
Since they're not here anymore. it's
only natural for us to take the gold.
It"s not "us"!
The gold is mine!
That's right. the gold belongs to El Drago-sama.
- We all know it.
- Where are you going?
Trying to escape?
No... I need to go to the toilet.
Holding it in your bladder's not a good thing to do.
This guy's definitely suspicious.
Do you really know where the gold is?
Come on. guys. do I look
like someone who'd lie?
I'm a very trustworthy person.
Really?
Of course. that goes without saying.
I've never told a single lie ever since I was born.
Crap.
This is really bad.
If I don't find a chance to escape soon...
El Drago-sama!
What should we do?
The road ahead is blocked!
Hey. hey. are you serious?
We came this far only to change routes?
Don't worry.
Gorashi.
Out of my way.
Wh... what?
No way!
That thing was a piece of cake for Gorashi.
How adept!
We're back here again.
I told you so.
What are we gonna do now? We're lost!
Don't be angry.
Anyways. Woonan's castle should
be somewhere on this island.
All we have to do is find that.
In that case. why are we
walking around in circles?
If we knew where we are.
there wouldn't be a problem.
What does that mean?
Don't be impatient.
You'll get hungry.
Right.
You guys!
Amazing!
This is Woonan's castle.
Okay. where's the gold?
Where?!
My stomach growls.
It growls!
My stomach goes pa pi pu pe po!
That's how it goes.
What's that?
So you really don't know.
What should we do?
Kill him!
Hey. Kamesuke!
You betrayed me!
Who are you?
I am Josephine.
The granddaughter of
the Great Gold Pirate. Woonan!
Woonan's...?
Kamesuke. you told them. didn't you?
That the gold is hidden under this gate!
Under this gate?
Under the gate... Under the gate...
Lady Josephine. what should we do now?
If you continue to dig and dig for three
days straight. you'll find the gold.
Of course I would never tell you this...
Damn. I said too much...
You're overdoing lt...
It's not believable.
I see. so it's under this gate!
Hey!
Anyways. three days is plenty enough
for me to find the gold and run.
El Drago-sama. let's start digging!
In three days...
There's no need!
Ten seconds is enough.
It's coming. his devil power!
What?
Oh no. Nami! Run!
Usopp!
I'm okay!
What is he?
He's doing it again!
What the?
That's... that's Woonan's castle.
Then that's where Woonan is?
Woonan!
Tobio!
Hold on to Zoro!
This sound technique...
The Scream-Scream Fruit!
So it's a Devil Fruit?
They say it has the power to transform
sound into the power of destruction.
The rumors were right...
At this rate. Woonan's castle will be destroyed.
Who the heck went and
told him the gold was under there?
That would be you!
If I blow everything up.
the gold will eventually appear.
Shut up!
Shut up already. lion!
You're hurting my ears!
Lion?
Sorry. I goofed. I meant to say cat.
Who are you?!
Me? I'm Luffy.
The man who's gonna be King of the Pirates.
This guy tied to me is Zoro.
Hey.
Woonan! You there?! Answer if you are!
What are you talking about?
That guy died a long time ago.
You don't know that until you see him.
Even if there's only one
person that thinks he's still alive...
...then he may still be alive!
What kind of nonsense are you babbling about?
Hey. why are they chained together like that?
Move aside!
I'll protect Woonan's gold by myself!
Hey. hey...
On this island lies the precious gold which
Woonan risked his life to get...
I won't let evil men like you do as you please!
Leave this island at once!
Do you want to die that badly?
You bastard...
You're a pretty good swordsman.
But you can't stop me!
What's wrong with you?
If I had three swords. this bastard would be...
Hey Luffy. don't stop me! Let me kill him!
I'm not stopping you.
What was that?
What happened to Josephine and Kamesuke?
Eh? They're gone.
Luffy! Zoro!
What. what on Earth happened?
For crying out loud. what a bother.
Are you all right?
Done.
We're saved!
Hey Nami. can you lend me some money?
Why?
They didn't pay it.
Why don't you just pretend
not to remember? It's just oden.
Who's the boy?
Tobio.
Who's Tobio?
It's just Tobio.
That's not what I mean!
Woonan's castle.
I guess the gold is under all that rubble.
What? Are you after the gold too?
No. that's not what I mean.
The gold's Woonan's.
If he's still alive.
He's still alive!
The gold isn't there. Neither is Woonan.
How do you know?
Can't you tell? That castle doesn't have
any trace of anyone living there.
It must be a decoy.
Woonan is probably somewhere else.
That's the treasure map!
Treasure map?
Right. this is the legendary map left behind
by one of Woonan's comrades.
When did you?
Did you forget who I am?
Hey. what are you doing?
Just watch.
If my instincts are right. then there must...
Scorching?
That's right!
It's a pretty simple trick.
Look. something is showing up.
Th... This is...
Nami!
Now. let's head for the Grand Line!
Don't change the subject!
What are we going to do without a map?
The only clue about Woonan is gone...
Well. was there something written on that map?
Umm. I think... it said...
"The treasure sleeps."
"Look south of the hill."
"If the whale faces west.
the tail points to the east."
Eh. really?
Woonan's castle is to the east.
Other than that...
The tail is to the east?
Ahhh. it's not pointing to the east!
That means the end of it is...
That!
Don't get blown away!
If we climb up this cliff.
we'll definitely see Woonan's...
We'll be able to meet Woonan!
If he's still alive.
Either way. I'll be taking the gold.
Hey. are you all right?
I guess it's too hard for the kid.
No. it isn't...
If I quit now...
I won't be able to join Woonan's crew!
Don't struggle or we'll fall.
Hey. I found a good place for us to rest.
Grandpa?
Why are you guys here?
I see. the treasure map...
What are you doing here. Pops?
Burying treasure in the highest place has
always been his way of doing things...
On this island. this is the
only place he would do it.
Grandpa...
You knew about Woonan?
Have you met him before?
He and I were like brothers.
growing up in the same village.
Woonan! I knew you'd be here.
It's done. I made this myself.
That's enough. Ganzô.
Like I'd ever eat oden made by you.
What did you say?
How can you say that
without even tasting it?
When did you
become such a weakling?
Open your eyes. Ganzô!
What was that?
Look at this gold!
This is the gold my
father spent all his life earning!
His entire life!
He worked his entire life. and this is it!
I'm not going to live such a stupid life!
I'll become a pirate...
And I'll steal the gold from all the evil people!
Ganzô. come with me.
You're worthy of being my right hand man!
Gold. eh...? Pathetic.
What!?
Your old man was a good man.
He taught me how to make oden...
...and many other things.
Whatever. he was just a drunkard.
I noticed...
Gold doesn't laugh.
Doesn't drink.
Doesn't sing.
And it doesn't shed tears.
It's no different from a rock!
A rock?!
He said my oden was good.
That's when I decided.
That I'd bet my life traveling
the world to let people eat my oden.
Pathetic... Pathetic. pathetic!
You're going to waste your life on that?
A man's life should be spent on a great ambition!
Forget about that. vow on this pirate flag.
And come with me!
Let's gather all the gold in this world!
No!
You stubborn bastard!
What did you say?
Do you really think that
you can beat me. Ganzô?!
Damn it!
Woonan!
G-Good. Ganzô. don't let go.
Pull me up slowly.
Woonan... Are you okay?
Woonan...
I know...
At this rate your pirate flag will be torn.
What are you saying?
This wouldn't have happened if you didn't keep blabbering.
Woonan.
What now?
Treasure your ambitions.
Ganzô!!!
And...
Did... did you die?
He's still alive. you idiot!
By chance. a ship passed nearby at that time.
It was the first miracle in the village.
What. you didn't die?
-No d'oh!
When I woke up three
days after the incident.
Woonan had already
left the village on his journey.
And we've never seen each other since.
I didn't know that.
Grandpa knew...
The Woonan I remember
changed since.
That stubborn. obstinate man
wouldn't try my oden.
But now... I think he would eat it now.
This pot of oden which I've put my life into...
A pot of oden which you've put your life into?
Now. let's not waste our time here.
Or the oden will get cold.
Okay. let's go!
Right.
Let's go.
A hut!
Nothing here.
No way!
It's empty over here too.
Did Woonan really live here?
There aren't any tables or chairs...
There's only a very common fireplace.
That's amazing. how did you find that?
Any idiot should be able to find this!
Hey look. you can go down from there.
A basement.
Woonan should be down there. then.
Along with his mountain of gold.
Duck!
"If the whale faces west.
the tail points to the east."
What a bunch of crap!
Ah. crap...
El Drago-sama. there's an entrance here.
So the gold is down there.
Okay. you guys bring it out.
Aye!
Stop!
Pops!
Grandpa!
What's this? Gold?
Stop!
That is... the oden Grandpa
put his life into for Woonan.
You people... don't touch it.
Are you satisfied now?
You want to die that badly?
Tobio!
And who're you?
Delicious!
It's no doubt that Pops' oden
is the world's best.
I will not forgive you for this!
What are you babbling about?
Take care of them. Gorashi!
Zoro!
It looks like I'm his opponent.
Hey... That guy using the Three-Sword Style...!
Zoro!
That's the Pirate Hunter. Roronoa Zoro!
It doesn't matter who he is. There's no one
more skilled with swords than Gorashi.
Gorashi! Cut this guy into pieces!
I will give you 200 gold pieces for every cut!
If you kill him it'll be 500!
Damn. powerful strength.
Go. Gorashi! I'll give you 1000...
1000 gold pieces!
Zoro!
Die!
What are you ashamed of?
In your heart. you don't want to kill for that guy.
Isn't that what you're thinking?
Your eyes... tell me that you are ashamed
to draw your sword for gold.
You've given up the pride of wielding a sword!
Gorashi. why are you hesitating?
Kill him!
You definitely have skill.
But without the pride in your sword.
you have a slight hesitation.
And that split moment is the unmatched
difference between you and me!
I avoided hitting your vital points.
When you've regained the pride in your
sword. come and challenge me again!
I'll face you then.
I never knew he was so strong.
It's not over yet. It's too soon to be surprised.
Now it's your turn.
Bastard. now you've really angered me.
Oh crap! Run away!
What?
Get away!
It hit him directly!
Gum-Gum...
Rocket!
You... stop screwing around!
What on earth is...
Luffy ate one of the Devil Fruits.
The Gum-Gum Fruit.
And now he's a rubber man.
So he was a Devil Fruit user?
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
He did it!
No. wrong.
That hurts! Let go!
Hey! What're you doing?!
That jerk's copying my attack.
You!
This is bad! A rubber man's done for if he gets cut in half!
Luffy!
Gum-Gum...
Bell!
El Drago-sama!
All right!
Die!
Gum-Gum...
Gatling!!
Whip!!
El Drago-sama's golden armor...
...has shattered!
Amazing!
The gold is mine!
The... the gold is...
Gum-Gum...
Go!!!
Bazooka!
El... El Drago-sama has...
...lost.
Time for us to run away!
Let's run away!
Run!
Hey wait. stop!
That's what I was saying...
Thanks. Tobio.
That's right. Pops. I'm sorry.
l ate all of Woonan's oden.
Your stomach'll get upset
if you eat stuff like that.
My stomach's not gonna be upset.
I'm a pirate.
I finally get to meet Woonan.
It's here.
Behind this door... is Woonan.
I'm opening it...
This...
This is...
No way! This can't be Woonan!
It's a fake.
Woonan must be somewhere else.
Grandpa...
Hey. what's this?
No doubt about it. Woonan's handwriting.
"To the people who came here for the gold:"
"My name is Woonan."
"Formerly known as
the 'Great Gold Pirate'..."
Formerly? What does he mean by that?
"But now I'm just a man waiting to die."
"All the gold I've gathered has been
returned to its rightful owners."
"This was a battle."
"To fulfill my childhood dream..."
And to build a mountain of gold.
the likes of which have never been seen before.
But as I sit before it.
the words a man once said to me come to my mind.
"Gold can't laugh. it's just like a rock."
It's true.
The thing I devoted my entire life to...
It wasn't the gold.
It was the adventure to find the gold.
"There's no gold here anymore."
"But instead. a treasure
that's even more valuable."
"To others. this might be worthless."
"But to me. this is plenty."
"Please do not destroy this place."
"This is where my
most precious treasure sleeps."
Ganzô...
Since the day you saved my life...
Deep in my heart. I've always believed
that you were on the same boat as I was.
by my side through all these adventures.
Because of this...
I have no regrets about living my life this way.
Woonan.
My goodness. your grandpa's a great man!
He is the only person in
which the legendary pirate trusted!
One is a great pirate.
One sells oden.
But...
They had the same pride.
Grandpa...
I... I'm...!
Sorry!
Tobio...
Live the way you want to live.
And I'll... always protect you.
Are you guys leaving already?
Yeah.
What will you guys do?
After we build a grave for Woonan.
I'll continue my oden shop.
So. do you still want to be a pirate? Or...
Sell oden?
I'll think about it the next time I leave home.
If I live my life seriously like Grandpa.
I'm sure I'll find the answer one day.
Right?
Right.
Where did you?
El Drago's treasures. I took them all!
You never change. do you.
That's right.
Here. This is the money
for what those two ate.
It's a loan.
A loan?
Of course. I expect three times the return.
Why you...
No. I can't accept the money now.
I've talked about it with Tobio.
and you will owe us the money.
Without interest.
This is so that we will be able to meet again.
Now. what are you guys still doing here?
Sail off while the weather is still good!
You eat and run bastards!
Good bye!
Don't forget about the great Captain Usopp!
Take care of yourselves!
We'll meet again!
He...
...really is gonna become the Pirate King.
Maybe.
Thank you. everyone!
Thank you. Luffy!
chiisana koro ni wa takara no chizu ga atama no naka ni ukandeite
When I was little. I had a vision of a treasure map
itsudemo sagashita kiseki no basho o
and I always searched for that miraculous place
shiranai dare ka ni makenai yô ni
before someone else could beat me to it.
itsudemo sagashita kiseki no basho o
and I always searched for that miraculous place
before someone else could beat me to it.
shiranai dare ka ni makenai yô ni
ima de wa tame iki tsuite bakari de dare mo mada
And everybody's still unable to stop sighing
hontô no yume-sae tsukamenai mama
If the world is going to change
moshi mo sekai ga kawaru no nara
before I can even attain my dream
nani mo shiranai koro no watashi ni
then take me to the time when I knew nothing
tsurete itte omoide ga iro-asenai yô ni
so that my memories won't fade
tsurete itte setsunasa ga oitsukanai yô ni
and so my loneliness won't catch up...